modelsoftheworld.com 2007-10-05

# modelsoftheworld.com - The Web Portal of models of the World

Privacy Policy

By this notice, Models of the World Corporation Inc, hereafter, informs the Users on the personal information protection policy (“Personal Information”) so that the Users can decide for themselves whether wish to provide **modelsoftheworld.com** their Personal Information that may be required of them or that could be obtained through the use by the Users of the services provided on line

**modelsoftheworld.com** reserves the right to change this policy to adapt it to changes in legislation or jurisdiction, and to practice of the industry. On this supposition **modelsoftheworld.com** will announce on its Web Site of any changes introduced with reasonable anticipation to its coming into force.

**modelsoftheworld.com** will provide its Users the appropriate technical resources, so that in privacy, they can access this notice on Protection of Information Policy or to any other pertinent information, and can authorize **modelsoftheworld.com** for the purpose of dealing automatically with Personal Information.

Personal Information will be the object of automatic treatment by **modelsoftheworld.com**. The User may give his prior consent through the technical resource that **modelsoftheworld.com** will provide, for the purpose of having **modelsoftheworld.com** can proceed to treat the Personal Information. The User warrants that the Personal Information provided to **modelsoftheworld.com** , is truthful and presently valid. The User should advise **modelsoftheworld.com** of any change in the same. The providing of additional information on Personal Information required is absolutely optional for the User..

The compiling and automatizing of the Personal Information has, as an only purpose, the maintenance of the contractual relationship, in the case established with **modelsoftheworld.com** , management, administration, provision, broadening and improving the services for which the User decided to subscribe or use the updating of such services for the preference and taste of the Users, the study of the use of services by the Users, the design of new services related to such services, the sending of updates of services, the sending by traditional and electronic means , of technical, operative and commercial information about the products and services offered by **modelsoftheworld.com** now and in the future. The purpose of compiling and automatizing the treatment of Personal Information also includes the sending of survey questionnaires that the User is not under obligation to answer..

For the purpose of providing an appropriate protection for the Personal Information, **modelsoftheworld.com** deals with it in conformity with the provisions of American legislation. To prevent unauthorized access , to keep the reliability of the Personal Information and to warrant the correct use of the same, we have put into practice physical, electronic, and appropriate management procedures to safeguard and secure the Personal Information that **modelsoftheworld.com** compiles in its card system

**modelsoftheworld.com** may cede the Personal Information to subsidiary companies of the Models Corporation of the United Status of America Inc, whose Web Site is available at the following URL: [http://www.modelsoftheworld.com](http://www.modelsoftheworld.com/) with the same purpose previously indicated for compiling of personal information by **modelsoftheworld.com**. At the time of compiling Personal Information to be ceded; and the Users will be duly informed of the particulars of the cessionaries, activities that realize and the purpose of the cession.

The rights of the Users are acknowledged and may exercise their rights of access, cancellation, rectification and opposition, as well as acknowledging their right to be informed of the cessions made by contacting **modelsoftheworld.com** through [legal@modelsoftheworld.com](mailto:legal@modelsoftheworld.com). 

The **modelsoftheworld.com** Web Site may contain links to other sites operated by third parties. **modelsoftheworld.com** is not responsible for the policies or practices on privacy of such sites.

If you wish to contact us for any reason related to privacy practices, write to us at the following e-mail address: [legal@modelsoftheworld.com](mailto:legal@modelsoftheworld.com).
